Testing API Key: AIzaSyAV1D...
Trying v1beta flash...
Status: 404
Response: {"error":{"code":404,"message":"models/gemini-1.5-flash is not found for API version v1beta, or is not supported for generateContent. Call ListModels to see the list of available models and their supp...
Trying v1 flash...
Status: 404
Response: {"error":{"code":404,"message":"models/gemini-1.5-flash is not found for API version v1, or is not supported for generateContent. Call ListModels to see the list of available models and their supporte...
Trying v1beta pro...
Status: 404
Response: {"error":{"code":404,"message":"models/gemini-pro is not found for API version v1beta, or is not supported for generateContent. Call ListModels to see the list of available models and their supported ...
Trying v1 pro...
Status: 404
Response: {"error":{"code":404,"message":"models/gemini-pro is not found for API version v1, or is not supported for generateContent. Call ListModels to see the list of available models and their supported meth...
